Guide to the Harols Hotelling Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XI: Employment and Biographical
  - Refugees and Other Europeans (wanting jobs) (Box 50)
  - Research Men in Stochastic Process (Box 50)
  - Secretarial Prospects (Box 50)
  - Students and Ex-Students Wanting Jobs (Box 50)
  - Certificates (Box 51)
  - Biographical materials (Box 51)
  - Clippings (Box 51)
  - Financial/Personal (Box 51)
  - Passports and secutiry clearance (Box 51)
- Series XII: Printed Material
  - Works by Hotelling (Box 52 & 53)
  - Works by other authors (Box 54 - 58)
  - Works by other authors (Box 55)
  - Works by other authors (Box 56)
  - Works by other authors (Box 57)
  - Works by other authors (Box 58)